Wait a minute. You're saying that this is...
Yeah, the demon from 15 years ago.
I always figured it was destroyed along with everything else in Heaven's Fall.
Captain Magburetch, look!
What in God's name is that?
Confirm ship's readiness. Check fuel, munitions, power status, and all systems.
Yes, ma'am!
Deucalion. That's the vessel's name.
What possible reason is there?
A ship like this abandoned, without ever going to battle?
Systems seem to be intact. With power, we should be good.
Current fuel levels are at? I'm not sure.
Is that supposed to be your report?
But ma'am, there's no fuel gauge!
And so that would be the reason.
The reason why they just abandoned this ship.
You mean that's...
An old Noah drive.
Sorry. Military only. Civilians aren't allowed here.
I'm afraid you'll have to leave.
Sorry.
Stay where you are!
There's no cause for alarm.
Please understand, I really am your friend.
This means you are.
In the name of Asalem vs. Lucia, hear my command.
Al Noah, awaken now!
Oh!
And now!
clothing
Doha tomuzu ga hoshi wo so mete
yo ku niji wo e prestige
Kiri te mabushu ni yori kimi ga Council
Ta udeal금,,,
Kire
Oh
Welcome back
Are you feeling any more talkative?
Now you'll tell me what you hope to reap from this
What was your reason for traveling there?
Yes
No
Perhaps he's had enough Count Cruteo
For the moment at least
Members of the lower races are not deserving of our pity
My lord Sazbo
After all we will learn nothing should you kill him
We have created an audience with the Emperor
Heedless of the possible risk to himself in the process
I wish to know his real intentions
Real intentions
As if this child were capable of a reasoning thought
My lord Count Cruteo
The island
We have an orbital night cataphract
You what?
We think it is Countess Femian's Hellas
Impossible
What brought about the death of Countess Femian
This is a waste of time
Count Cruteo
That's quite enough
You will tell me now
Then I will put you out of your misery
Then continue to suffer
So this is the bridge
The Deucalion
A flying battleship
Nina
What is it that makes it able to fly?
Oh yeah, it's that Martian thing
You mean old Noah?
Yeah, that's it
Do the helm controls work like on a normal ship?
I mean, do you really think you can handle this thing?
The flight control system has been adjusted
So yeah, it feels just the same as when I steer the other ship
Sure you should be away from your post right now, Calm?
Hey, what's the big deal if I want to look around the ship a little bit?
It's not like there's any brass around
Wait, where's he not home?
He got called into the captain's office
At the same time as the Martian did
The Martian did too?
Yeah
Because of her the old Noah drive is working
And I got the helm
What?
So the Mars Knights are responsible for the assassination plot?
That's hard to accept
Captain Magbarej
If we were to disclose this information
Then maybe the Mars Knights would cease their attacks
All of our telecom centers and comm satellites are gone
And their jamming signal prevents any long-range transmission
If we tried to send word that the Princess was still alive
We couldn't be sure the message would get to the right parties
And so you think that might put us on the radar of the Mars Knights
Who plotted her assassination?
Tactically, we were going to make our way to UFE headquarters in Russia to regroup anyway
So until then, we shall be seeing to your safety, your highness
I thank you so much
Now as for you, young Kaiska
Inaho Kaiska, ma'am
And young lady?
Raihei Ariyash
The two of you
You were fully aware of this situation, yet you neglected to inform me
Since I am not in the military, I am not obligated
And you, young Kaiska?
It was not a matter of any neglect
It was a deliberate choice I made
You had better watch what you're saying
Because you're on extremely thin ice here
I asked him to keep my secret
Someone working with the assassins could be on the ship right now
And we have no way of-
Del Rizzo!
And we sure can't trust you Martians very far either
You're a society bound by an archaic feudal system
That relies on the super science of a dead civilization
Commoners obsessed with combat as a pathway to social status
And nobility who will always see them as inferior
And people like that
They only know how to betray
I will never trust them
Every last Martian is the enemy to me
Regardless of scientific advances, there are some primitive techniques we retain
Because there are occasions when they can be quite effective
Do it
Does that hurt?
Speak
What was that?
You...
Oh...
Did that one loosen up your tongue?
Do you...
Swear your loyalty to...
The royal princess...
Salem...
Continue
Yes sir
You wretched impotent boy
So lieutenant, how are you feeling?
Lousy actually
Back to normal
Medication seems to be working well
Not a great time for the PTSD to come back
I'd feel better a lot faster if you let me wet my whistle
Not exactly the kind of stuff I usually prescribe
Service here sucks
Birds?
Yes
Creatures that fly through the air
If I go to earth, I will be able to see some, won't I?
Oh yes
It's quite slow but...
The scars from heaven's fall are all starting to fade
Nature is quite a powerful force
An area is swept clean, and then nature comes in to reclaim it
You mean when all the people disappear?
Exactly
Unlike urban areas, all the damaged regions provide an environment where plants can...
It's sad, isn't it?
That people cannot coexist with the natural world
Well that's not true at all
With some planning and hard work, I believe we could do it
Is that possible, really?
Oh yes!
We could certainly live in harmony together
So I'll ask again, feel like sharing anything with me now?
Count Cruteo, do you care at all for her highness the princess?
What?
You consider yourself...
To be her ally?
Yes, absolutely I am
But now you must speak
Or as punishment for what you have done
Your compatriots on earth will know horrors more than you can imagine
I knew you were lying
The only thing you want
Is an excuse to go to war with earth
What her highness wished for
Was there to be peace with earth
But you...
You only want to use her murder
To exploit her death
And crush her dream
Do not invoke her memory
You do not have the right, you filthy Terran
Salem?
Yes?
Oh, I mean Princess of Salem
You may call me Salem, Inaho
I do not mind
I certainly do mind
From now on you say your highness and bow
Adele Ritzo
Purple lady!
I apologize for her
This is just her way of trying to safeguard my welfare
You were about to say something?
Yes, I met someone on Tanegashima and...
Hey, Inaho!
Listen to this!
I just found out
Did you know there were Martians here on the ship with us?
Yes
Okay, where can I find them?
Where are they? I'm gonna avenge Okujo!
We are right here
I am the one that you seek
Um...
You are?
I deeply regret all that has occurred
The many deaths
And all the harm to the innocent
I assure you the Verse Empire does not want this war
I am doing all I possibly can to bring this senseless conflict to an end
Oh...
Uh...
Well then...
Good luck to you!
Why are you blushing about calm?
You're lobster red
Where'd you two come from?
Weren't you going on about getting some revenge?
Yeah, didn't you say something about how every Martian was the enemy?
No, I certainly never said that
You ought to be ashamed
There are good Martians and bad Martians
They're people, right Inaho?
Back me up, man!
Huh?
Just as I said, milady, you cannot trust Terrans
Inaho
Inaho, you have helped me so many times since I came to Earth
Thank you very much
To be fair, your protection wasn't my primary motivation
It's because they drafted me
If I refused to fight, it would have endangered us all
Regardless, you have come to my rescue so many times
And I am grateful
There was a Martian I met on Tanegashima
He was there in an effort to find you
He was concerned that both sides might be trying to exploit you
Could that offend?
Among the enemy
There are undoubtedly some who think that you're still alive
I suggest that you stay on your guard
Hmm
What is that?
A good luck charm given to me by a dear Terran friend when I left for Earth
A dear Terran friend?
The son of a scientist who visited Verse to study old Noah
It was from him I heard all manner of stories regarding Earth
About the sea?
About the sky?
About the wonderful creatures who live here?
As I listened to his stories, I was completely enchanted
I wanted nothing more than to come and see it for myself
Also, I wanted to bring about lasting peace with Earth
That creature there, is that a bird?
Yes, black-tailed gull
Animals that fly through the air
They really do exist, don't they?
Yes, Slane, it's just like you told me
You told me
So long ago
My life was saved by Princess Asalem
If it were not for her
I would surely not be alive today
So now, regardless of the cost
I will protect you, your highness
I must not tell anyone that she is alive
I cannot allow those who hope to exploit the princess
To have their way
Whether they are Martian
Or they are Terran
I won't
Princess Asalem would have been heartbroken
To see how her misplaced faith in this swine
Would cost her life
Count Kuteo, sir
Yes, what is it?
We found something very odd on the island
Wreckage of another cataphract
Which is not Countess Femian
No, it can't be
The one lost on Earth?
From 15 years ago
You mean the Deucalion?
Is it real?
It seems that the unit's Alt Noah drive has been removed
What?
All right
There's no reason for alarm
Terrans don't have the ability to activate Alt Noah
Is there something that you find to be amusing?
No, nothing
We are through here
Kill him
Wait, Captain Kuteo
The proud orbital knights
Will not stand for his mockery
I will burn you to ashes here on Earth
Answer, dammit
What did you find to be so funny?
What were you laughing at?
Huh?
You will tell me
Without the aid of Alt Noah
The Terrans could not possibly have demolished the Hellas
This is punishment for all the things you've done
To kill her highness's dream of peace
That's nonsense
They have no way to activate it
Only a handful of Vercians have landed on Earth
And the only ones who could have activated it
It cannot be
Princess of Salem
Is her highness still alive?
Speak
Does she still live?
Answer me!
And if she were...
What would you do then?
Assassinate her again?
What's that?
Aren't you the one who...
Commanded Sir Trillram...
To end the princess's life?
You dare suggest I...
If we let her live...
My clan will be branded as traitors?
As I recall...
You made the claim of having witnessed his death
I did...
When I shot him
Then...
He was not caught in a meteor bombardment?
In the Nilokaris...
With its dimensional barrier?
Hmm...
I refuse...
To let you traitors have your way
Her highness...
Is going to...
Smash your plants...
Herself...
Ugh...
So Princess of Salem...
Is still alive then?
It's not possible...
It cannot be...
Somehow you learned this...
And searched for the princess yourself...
Telling no one...
To avoid alerting the traitors...
And with no support...
Accepting torture and death to keep her secret safe...
Forgive me, Slain...
Your loyalty is proven beyond measure...
See to this man's injuries right away!
Yes, sir!
I swore my loyalty to her highness...
The traitors who dared raise their hands against her...
Will pay dearly...
Put me through to the United Forces of Earth...
Announce a cease-fire to them...
And request their assistance in locating the princess...
The traitorous dogs who mocked the righteous orbital knights with this treason...
Will be punished!
Lord Cruteo!
There is an object approaching us from orbit!
What kind?
Another bombardment of meteors?
No!
It's decelerating!
It's a man's craft, my lord!
And now they're approaches...
The estimated point of impact...
This landing castle!
No!
It's a man's craft, my lord!
And now they're approaches altering!
The estimated point of impact...
This landing castle!
No!
It's a man's craft, my lord!
What the hell is happening?
That is...
The Dioscuria.
It's Count Sosbaum.
And so I see.
Everything is clear now.
You masterminded the assassination.
Ready my Tharsis!
Let's go.